<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thought Board DUCS</string>
    <string name="new_message">Create New Message</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="home_screen_menu">Home Screen Menu</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="thought_board">Thought Board</string>
    <string name="ducs">Department of Computer Science
        \n University of Delhi</string>
    <string name="made_with_love_by_ducs_developers">    Made With Love\nBy DUCS Developers</string>
    <string name="about_the_department">About the Department</string>
    <string name="about_description"> The Department of Computer Science was established in the year 1981 with the objective of imparting quality education in the field of Computer Science.
        The Department has modern facilities for teaching, learning and research. The Department offers a wide array of research opportunities and programs of study at undergraduate and postgraduate level.\n
        \nThe Department started 3-year Master of Computer Applications (MCA) programme in the year 1982, which was among the first such programmes in India.\n
        \nThe Department started 2-year M.Sc. Computer Science programme in the year 2004 with the aim to develop core competence in Computer Science and prepare the students to carry out development work, as well as take up challenges in research.\n
        \n\nBesides these, the Department offers Doctor of Philosophy (Ph.D.) in Computer Science aimed at producing quality researchers and high-impact interdisciplinary research.\n
        Undergraduate CBCS programmes - B.Sc. (H) Computer Science, B.Sc. Physical / Mathematical Sciences and B.A. Programme (Discipline Courses in Computer Applications) are offered by the University of Delhi through its constituent colleges.\n
        With rapidly evolving technology and the continuous need for innovation, the Department has produced quality professionals holding important positions in the IT industry in India and abroad.\n\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="message">Message</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="no_messages_found">No Messages Found!</string>
    <string name="tap_the_icon_to_create_one">Tap the + Icon to Create One</string>
</resources>